Emma Phuong Ng.

Knowledge Seeker. Stormborn. Outlier. GMAIL | LINKEDIN | GITHUB | TWITTER Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam | (+84) 963 091 560

SKILLS

DEEP LEARNING

- Convolutional Neural Networks
- Recurrent Neural Networks
- Auto-encoders
- Generative Adversarial Networks

APPLIED TOPICS

- Machine Translation
- Image Classification
- Object Recognition

MATHEMATICS

- Linear Algebra
- Statistics
- Probability Theory
- Applied Topology

PROGRAMMING

• Python: 6000+ hrs

TECHNOLOGY

- •Spark Hadoop Bazel
- AWS (EC2, S3, EMR)
- Azure Keras/Tensorflow Pytorch

ABILITIES

ANALYTICAL THINKING DESIGN THINKING CREATIVE THINKING

OTHERS

COMPETITION

Top 1% IA Healthcare Challenge Fabre Laboratories, France

HOBBIES

Travelling • Culture • Boardgames

SUMMARY

Researcher in Deep Learning with experience in Data Science and Big Data in 3 years. Familiar with Apache Spark and Pytorch, Keras and Tensorflow. Master of Math and Computer Science (2014). A world traveler. Open-source contributor. Pythonista.

PROJECTS

IMAGINATION - COMPUTER VISION

August 2017 till Now - On progress.

- Propose a method to learn representations of deep reinforcement framework.
- Work with PyTorch and multiple open-source packages with Anaconda.

EXPERIENCE

INDEPENDENT RESEARCHER | ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Aug 2015 - Present

• Research interest in Deep Generative and Computation Cognitive Models.

INSTRUCTOR | ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017 | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

 Collaborated with Med2Lab to design, build and conduct a pilot class of 14 students for teaching basic knowledge and skill in Python.

DATA SCIENTIST | TENPOINT7

Oct 2016 - Aug 2017 | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

• Researched, proposed and developed applications for Natural Language Processing Pipeline as a part of company's product.

DATA SCIENCE FELLOW | GALVANIZE - A LEARNING COMMUNITY

Aug - Oct 2016 | San Francisco, USA

• A 13-week intensive program working on data technologies and machine learning with case studies including churn analysis and fraud detection.

RESEARCHER | SINGAPORE MANAGEMENT UNIVERSITY

April 2016 - Aug 2015 | Singapore

 Investigated a theoretical framework of privacy for database by doing mathematics and working on computer science information theory.

MANAGING DIRECTOR | INSPI CORP. - A SOCIAL MEDIA START-UP July 2014 - April 2015 | Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

• Managed and led 5 core members to create a viral product pioneering in the local market with around 3,000,000 views after 3 months.

RESEARCH INTERN | L'ÉCOLE POLYTECHNIQUE

April 2014 - July 2014 | Palaiseau, France

• Built a computational model to study biological structure of a neural network in brain gray matter by MATLAB and FORTRAN90.

EDUCATION

NANO DEGREE | ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

1st Cohort, 2017 @ Udacity

MASTER OF SCIENCE | MATHS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

2013-2014 @ University of Paris 13 | France

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | MATHS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

2009 - 2013 @ Vietnam Nat'l University | Vietnam